So you've already seen those last few
videos so pretty much so I just want to
run through like a
short demo with you of the actual site and
the back office so when we actually jump
on the call
you have everything that you need in order
to get rocking and rolling.
So pretty much I'm just going
to briefly go over RevTech rentals here
for you guys this is one of our existing
clients they've
been with us for the last six months and I
want to show off these guys' size because
one it looks
absolutely amazing but two because they've
done something good job in configuring
everything
exactly how they want to run their
business which is the whole point of
Drive247 right taking control
back for your business. So obviously here
is their existing system so this is their
site with their
logo their name, their about you page,
their fleet and pricing, reviews,
promotions, FAQs,
contacts and blogs. Okay absolutely
everything has been custom built out and
personalized
for them on this site which means they
have a brand they have their own solid
site
which means when the custom boots and
there's more trust built out.
So just to go through as a customer
here we can obviously select for a few
different pickup locations.
Now as the host you have a few
different options where obviously your
customers can pick up and return the
vehicles because you
have like a static or you can have the
option to deliver it to a specific
location i .e. the airport
or to a hotel like these guys do but also
you have the option to deliver it to a
specific
address within a tiered area so 10 bucks
for 2 miles away 50 bucks for 20 miles
away whatever
it is right you have that option. So
obviously your customers come through here
select the pickup
the return locations with the day and time
obviously that they want to rent in.
The most
important thing they can go through and
it's all done on a real -time calendar.
Let's say you have
10 vehicles that you want to rent out and
that you have available.
Five of them are already out
with existing customers that means that
the calendar is real -time updated and
it's only
going to show the five vehicles which are
actually available in your current fleet.
So they select the
date and time if the vehicles are
available then they can go ahead they can
select one of those
they can then go to insurance on this tab
here where they can enter in their own
personal policy
it'll be verified and scanned through the
whole system the AI which is already built
in there
for you or they can actually go ahead and
they can purchase external insurance
through Bonsa.
Now these guys are a partner with us so
they've been on us since pretty much
inception
so we've got a super great relationship
with them but what it also means is you
can offer out
insurance to your customers when they're
booking so you can offer out you know CDW
or CLI you can
offer it as a bundle you could do the you
know the supplementary liability on there
as well
and your customers can purchase insurance
direct through your sign through Bonsa
because it's
all built -in integration it's already in
the box so as soon as you get set up with
your system
it's going to be in there. The only thing
you have to go set up an account with them
obviously is you are providing insurance
they need to have your details but they go
through
the engine their customer details i .e
their address their phone number their
location their
you know name and everything right that
data one you have it captured anyway to
build loyalty
customer base promotions anything like
that but also it means it automatically
does the insurance
for you as well so they go through they
upload all of that information then they
are prompted with
a driver's license identification so they
upload the front and the back of the
driver's license
they take a selfie it's going to go
through all of that data which they just
uploaded process
it all with the AI built -in and it's
going to verify everything for you once
they get
the green light they can then review and
confirm automatically you get a rental
agreement
sent over to their email for ready for an
e -signature you get a rental invoice
generated
for them and they also get a rental
summary as well this you don't have to
touch it's
already done for you to save you going to
another software save you having to fap
about and do it
yourself once that's all done everything
is ready to be paid just simple stripe
check out once they
pay everything the whole flow is completed
you haven't even had to touch the thing
to get the
customer rented in and then you can see
everything on the backup it's here so this
is one of our
demo accounts actually which is why there
is really isn't much business activity
going on here
but there's a full proprietary AI built
out into the system which can do actions
check all your
data and help you learn and navigate the
system following that we can see all of
our vehicles
all of our rentals from the calendar view
for the week for the month or just from
this view here
it should be actually clicking we can see
all of this information in terms of rental
pickups handovers
mileage summaries insurance verification
everything is in there from customers we
can catch all of
this data as well you can block anyone and
also you can just do in -app messaging so
saves you
having 50 different contacts in your phone
trying to juggle emails from juggle text
messages to make
sure if they need to pay if they're going
to return the vehicle you have it all in
here in one
place with the emails calling sms or
whatsapp as well all of your payments you
can see all of these
here all time invoices any fines as well
as you know related to customers expenses
so you can
almost use this accounting as well
specific for your business whether it's
insurance whether it's
tolls whether it's valet each month get AI
summaries and also it will show you
absolutely
everywhere that you're spending your your
minute your money so insurances this is
where you can
keep track of all of these along with your
agreements your reminders and reporting
across
the board for each specific customer each
specific vehicle now it wouldn't be a
system
didn't have a full -on profit in us across
the whole board so you can see obviously
globally
tracked from month from year each vehicle
profitability how much you're actually
putting in and how much your total costs
are we don't just stop there with like
building the
system out for you have full autonomy and
customization and control over your site
so if you ever wanted to tweak anything
whether it's you know the images on the
front page whether
it's the headline or the sub header you
can obviously go ahead and do that as well
now for the guys who have like a few
different users maybe you're running a
business with two
three four other people and you want to
have them inside and not just keep on
sharing each
other's passwords you can set each other
up with other managers operations admins
just means that you can simultaneously
both be inside the system and using the
platform
now this is just where you kind of
configure everything and this is something
more for
the actual call where we go through
everything and sort of figure out the game
plan but this
is obviously where you can go through your
locations all of your branding how long
they
can rent out the vehicle for pricing rules
fees pre -authorization on the cards
instalments
pay as you go then of course notifications
emails and rental agreements as well
so yeah wanted just to to run through
actual live system and do that
if you have any other questions I'm sure
save them for the call but make sure you
join from a laptop just how I am on the
desk make sure we're ready for a proper
conversation
see you inside